金妍儿-花痴字幕组
听译/时间轴/压制：UZDA
协助: Joanna Sheep Tracy
www.weibo.com/yunakim
冰上圆舞曲
Hey, Dad. I'm back
爸  我回来了
I'm starving. What you doing?
我好饿    你在做什么？
Next year's planting
明年的计划
I'm trying to figure out what's the best cash crop. Trying to.
我想找出快速赚钱的最佳方法
Every year it gets harder to outsmart the market
赚钱一年比一年难
So, how was the pond?
池塘好玩吗？
It was good
挺好玩的
Listen, I've been thinking about graduation
我最近在考虑你毕业后的事
Yeah. I haven't
我还没
Yeah, well, I know that
嗯，我知道
We gotta start thinking about what colleges...
我们该开始考虑哪所大学...
Nick is coming home
Nick要回来了
Okay. And what does that have to do with college?
好，但这跟大学有什么关系？
Nick goes to college
Nick 在外读大学
he's home for a pick-up game tonight at the rink
回家是为了今晚在冰场的比赛
When you go to college, you're supposed to stay there until you darn well graduate
当你去上大学 在毕业之前应该呆在那
Do you wanna come?
你要去吗？
I think I'm gonna try to get a little practice in beforehand
我想在比赛前练习一下
Well, that I wouldn't miss for the world
当然要去
You got to pull in tighter, if you're gonna turn that into a triple
如果要做三周 手脚要更靠紧一些
There he is. Nick Peterson—last year's Eastern MVP
这不是Ncik Peterson嘛  去年东区最有价值选手
Too bad nobody saw it
没人看到真可惜
You saw it
你看到了
Who cares?
谁在乎？
Back from Michigan State for a potential career-ending injury in a few pick-up games with his boyfriends
因为队友练习赛导致可能断送职业生涯的受伤  从密西根州归来
Do you still skate like a girl or what?
你还是像女孩般滑冰吗？
Yeah. And you know, now we actually wear dresses at Michigan State
当然 我们很纯洁的 现在甚至都穿着密歇根州时的衣服
That's my boy, I think 真乖啊
You want a coffee?  要喝咖啡吗？
You actually came
你真的来了
Yeah. I gotta show these boys a thing or two
当然    我得让这些小朋友见识一下
Bring your homework?
带作业了吗？
With you here, are you kidding me?
你开玩笑吗？
Are you learning anything besides hockey?
你除了冰球你还学别的吗？
No, 'cause I'm going pro
不 因为我要转职业选手
Hey, so was that a double or triple you just did?
你刚刚做的是两周跳还是三周？
Triple
三周跳
What?!
什么?!
[everybody, clear the ice Everybody off the ice. Thank you]
[各位注意   清场了 谢谢]
[But you're all welcome to stick around for the Ashton's pick-up game but we need everybody off the ice right now Thank you
欢迎大家留下来看Ashton冰球练习赛 但现在请大家离开冰场 谢谢]
The Lowa Invitational Junior Championships are in Cedar Rapids this weekend
爱荷华州青少年邀请赛本周末在Cedar Rapids市举行
Yeah. I saw the posters for it.You want to go?
恩      我看到了海报了   你要去吗？
I want you to sign up
我要你去报名参赛
Yeah, right
好
You've been skating since you can walk.You're darn good
从你会走路时就开始滑冰   你滑的非常好
Maybe it's time you show someone
也许是该让大家看看的时候了
What's the point?
为什么?
The point is I know my sister
我很清楚我妹妹的想法
She always thought you could do more than skate around that darn pond. Compete.
她认为你不仅能在冰池塘上滑冰 可以做到更多—参加比赛
I just do it for fun now
我现在滑冰只是因为兴趣
We can use the program we used for Christmas
我们可以用圣诞节的那套节目
the one your mother played
你妈妈表演过的那套
But I don't wanna do it
但是我不想
Come on!  give me a chance to cheer you on for a change
别这样！  给我一个给你加油的机会
Hey, Let's play. Come on
嘿 来嘛 我们来玩
Polo 波罗
Marco 马可
Come on. You'll have fun if you go
去比赛吧  如果你去了你会玩的很开心
You're gonna be at school, though
但是你会在学校
I know But I'll come back
我知道 但我会回来的
Marco 马可
Polo 波罗
You took it off
你偷看
Hey, you're going 你会去的
No 不要
Yes, you are 去嘛
Give it back
还给我
You're gonna regret it if you don't go
不去你会后悔的
All right
好吧
I haven't been to Cedar Rapids in a while
我好久没去Cedar Rapids（比赛地）了
That's my girl
这才对嘛
Ladies and gentlemen
there is someone very special here today
女士们先生们 今天有贵客光临
Let's give a big Cedar Rapids welcome to Olympic silver medallist Aiden Reynolds!
让我们热烈欢迎奥运银牌得主Aiden Reynolds!
Hey, how you doing?
还好吗？
I'm all right
挺好的
Are you having fun yet?
玩的开心吗？
I'm nervous
我很紧张
Keep breathing
深呼吸
She's really good
她真的很棒
Scores for Carol Sanders.
Technical, 39.92 Components, 38.88 For a composite score of 78.80
Carol Sanders得分：技术分39.92 节目内容分38.88 总分78.80
Our next competitor, representing Ice Castle Skating Club in Windsor, Iowa is—
下一位参赛者 代表爱荷华温莎冰上城堡俱乐部—
Lexi Winston!
That explains her outfit
难怪穿成这样
Have fun, okay?
享受比赛吧
Hey. I love you. 我爱你
I love you, too. 我也爱你
I didn't know she was gonna skate to this piece
我不知道她会用这首曲子
Your mom would have been so proud,so proud
你母亲会很自豪 很自豪
Scores for Miss Winston. Technical 30.25
Winston小姐得分：技术分30.25
Components, 41.76
节目内容分 41.76
Oh, come on. That's horrible
拜托 这什么打分
For a combined total of 72.01
总分为72.01
A wonderful effort nonetheless
精神可嘉
You coached that new girl, right?Carrie something?
你是那个新冠军的教练是吗？叫Carrie什么的？
We're no longer working together
我们已经不再合作了
I take it you haven't competed much
你想你参加的比赛不多
She was great
她很棒
I didn't say she wasn't.
but everything she was doing was level one
我没说她不好       但是她的表现只能算是初级
With the right training, hard work,and a higher profile I think you could be a serious competitor
好的训练加刻苦努力以及多亮相,我相信你可以在比赛中崭露头角
I just skate for fun
我只是滑着玩
It showed
看的出来
Think how much fun you'd have if you won
想想你赢了之后会更多乐趣
She did just fine
她做的很好了
She could do better
她可以做的更好
You owe it to yourself There's a whole world out there
你欠自己一个机会   外面的世界这么大
Wouldn't it be nice to see how far you can go?
看看你自己能走多远不是很好吗？
Mr Winston, your daughter is a natural on the ice
Winston先生 你的女儿很有花滑天赋
I'm guessing she's a bit late in the game. but she's also got the strength and poisethe younger girls don't have
我想她起步晚了 但是她的力量和姿态都是年轻女孩不具有的
She can land a triple
她可以做三周跳
That's good
这很好
But skating today is a total package: athleticism, emotion, and glamour
但是花滑现在需要具有几个条件：竞技、情感、魅力
Lexi's got two out of three
Lexi拥有两种
It may sound cynical,but that's just the way it is
也许听起来有些悲观 但现实就是如此
You really want to coach me?
你真的想当我教练吗？
Regionals are coming up.
There's barely enough time to train,but I'm willing to give it a shot
地区赛快开始了 几乎没足够的训练时间了 但是我愿意试试
附：全美锦标赛 Regional(地区)→Sectional(分区)→National（全国）
Are you? It's your life.
你觉得呢? 你自己决定吧
Thank you 谢谢
You train at Boston Memorial Rink, right?
你在波士顿纪念冰宫训练,对吗？
I do.If I don't hear from you by tomorrow,I'll move on.
是的  如果明天没有你的答复  我就离开
My dad will be all by himself
那样就只剩我爸一个人了
Your dad is a sharp guy, I think he'll survive
你爸是聪明人 我相信他会过的很好
Look, I gotta get going
我得走了
He hasn't been alone since my mom died
我妈妈过世后他就没有一个人过
You planning on living with your dad for the rest of your life?
你打算一辈子都陪着你爸？
What about us?
那我们呢？
I'll tell you one thing,I'm not moving in with him
我告诉你我不会跟他住一起
I'm serious
我是认真的
You and me, we're like a rock
你和我坚如磐石
And plus I'm gonna be at school most of the time.
加上我以后大部分时间都在学校
Which reminds me, if I don't get going right now,
I'm gonna drive off the road
这提醒我了如果现在不走 等下就无法开车
But you'll miss me too much
你会很想我吧
Well, maybe
也许吧
You know I always miss you when you're out of sight
你知道每当我看不到你我都会很想你
And we'll see each other in a few weeks
when you come down for our first game
等我们的第一场比赛 我们几星期内就可以见面
You know,I'm kind of exciting, you and me—
我都有点兴奋了 你和我—
famous Red Wings star
and world...Hey, Olympic champion figure skater
一个将是著名红翼队选手   一个将是花样滑冰世界..恩...奥运冠军
Think fast!
接招!
Stop Nick!
住手 Nick!
Oh, my God, you are dead. You are dead!
噢 天啊 你死定了 你死定了！
You must be Lexi
你就是Lexi吧
You're gonna have to work on closing your mouth when entering the hotel
进酒店时请别张大嘴巴
Sorry. I'm just that...
对不起  我只是....
金妍儿→
I know. I'm just all too much
我知道  这实在高大上
Just wait
等一下
We are part of the hotel,but we're just kind of off by ourselves.
我们的场地只是酒店的一部分 但只有我们自己使用
Everybody's really nice. But you're the new girl, so...
每个人都很好   但是你是新来的所以.....
it's her. Oh, please
就是她  哦 拜托
Everybody has their own room
每个人都有自己的房间
We eat in the slum section of one of the hotel coffee shops
我们在酒店咖啡馆的低价区里用餐
And don't even think about escaping into town for a good dinner
别想逃到城里吃大餐
because you're gonna be working all the time
因为你们一直都要训练
We have the workout room,aerobics, strength, stretch
我们有练习室    有氧、力量、柔韧训练
Big deal for Mr Reynolds
Reynolds先生很重视这里
Does everyone here train with him?
这里的选手都跟他训练吗？
←金妍儿
No, there are several coaches that use Boston Club as a base
不 这里有许多教练都在波士顿俱乐部执教
So what's the big deal about Carrie Turner?
Carrie Turner是怎么回事？
You don't get a lot of news in Idaho, huh?
你在爱达荷不太知道外面的事吧？
Iowa 是爱荷华
Same difference 都一样偏僻
Carrie jumped ship last week to train with Frank Carroll
Carrie上周就跳槽到Frank Carroll教练门下
right after she took first in the Colorado Invitational 就在她赢得科罗拉多邀请赛冠军之后
Coach is pretty bent up about it,so I'm not sure I'd bring it up
教练非常生气 也许我不该告诉你这事
We have two full-time physical trainers
我们有两名全职体能训练师
They also do massage
so if you pull something, it gets fixed fast
他们也会按摩
如果你有拉伤 他们会马上处理
Not a lot of wasted time
不要浪费时间
And some ballet
还要练习芭蕾
Hey, look, I know you're from Ohio or somewhere,
but this is real life, okay?
听好 我知道你是从俄亥俄或某些地方来的  但这里很现实
You want to do something,you want to get somewhere?
你想有所表现?你想有所成就？
This is your chance. Don't blow it
这是你的机会 别浪费了
Come on, Bret!
来吧,Bret！
Hit it
击球
Look, if you want this thing, you gotta get there!
听着 你要想赢 你就冲到那里！
Get your man. Get your man.
Peterson, you got him.
追上他 追上他 Peterson你制住他了
The coach is only as good as his best skater
教练的执教水平高低取决于他最好的弟子水平
He needs a new star and he's hoping
somebody he's working with here is gonna emerge
他需要一个新星 也希望他的弟子有人能脱颖而出
Emerge?
脱颖而出?
Yeah. A star to show she can take them all the way
是的 就是能一路带领大家前进的新星
All the way where?
前进到哪里？
Nationals. Worlds
全美锦标赛 世界锦标赛
Seriously?
真的吗？
Good morning, ladies. Welcome to Boston.Let's get to it.
女士们早上好 欢迎来到波士顿 我们开始训练吧
And, Lexi... ...you see those girls out there?Those coaches?
Lexi......看到那边那些女孩和教练了吗？
How you take the ice right now,the first time
你现在在这里开始滑冰 第一次的表现
is gonna go a long way in determining whether it's you or them skating here after regionals.
非常重要 那将会决定谁在地区赛后继续在这里滑冰
Did you see that?
你看到了吗？
She's replacing Carrie? 她要取代Carrie？
She is 是的
And we're off
我们可以开始了
That's cute
还不错
Hey, you. So I scored two goals today
嘿 我今天进了两球
Really? That's awesome.
真的 那太棒了
How's it going out there?
一切都好吗？
Good.It's kind of strange, but it's great.
很好 有点奇怪 可是很棒
It just takes a little getting used to,you know.
需要花点时间来适应
Mr Reynolds is a really great coach, though.
I had no idea I could skate like this.
Reynolds先生是很好的教练 我不知道自己能滑的这么好
We're both on the way up
我们都在进步
So I'm really looking forward to my first game so I can finally see you
真希望我的第一场比赛快点开始 这样我就可以见到你
To tell you the truth,I actually might not stay at school too long
说实话 我可能不会在学校待到毕业
If everything goes the way it looks,I might get drafted early.
如果一切顺利 我可能提早离开学校
That's great.
那太好了
Nick Peterson!
Well, I miss you
我会想你的
Okay, those turns need to be clean. Deeper
这些步伐转体需要更清晰一些 用刃深一些
More upper body. Come on, more drama
多点上肢动作  更戏剧一些
You need to be at least level 3 if you wanna be competitive
如果想要有竞争力 步伐需要达到三级以上
You've got regionals in less than three weeks
你只有不到三周的时间准备地区赛(小)
I want you going over these sequences every waking moment
我希望你无时无刻不在想着这些步伐动作
More drama! That's it! That's level three!
更多戏剧感!  就是那样! 三级步伐!
You gotta get there to be in the top four
otherwise you don't move on
你要在地区赛进入前4名 否则就没机会了
Good. No, it's looking better.
很好 不 这样更好
All right. Okay. Give us...Just go over it one more time
好的 让我们再练习一遍
Hey, it's Lexi. I'm probably skating, but if you leave me a message, I'll call you back
这是Lexi 我可能在滑冰 如果你留言 我会回电话
Hey, guys. Come here. It's Carrie. Oh, my God Carrie is back
各位看过来 这是Carrie 噢 我的天 Carrie回来了
Maybe she came back to say goodbye
也许她只是来道别
I doubt it. Just wait here
我很怀疑 在这等着
Call a break? You should be practicing.Go. Practice. Go. Go. Go.
谁说可以休息了 回去训练 回去 回去 回去
What are you doing here?
你来这干嘛？
That's the new girl?
那是新来的女孩？
Yeah, Lexi Winston
是的
I hear she's competing week after next
我听说她两周之后要比赛
Yeah, she is
是的 她要比赛
Talent pool is a little slim these days, huh?
看起来现在没什么人才?
Careful. It's slippery out there.
小心 场地很滑
Good luck
祝你好运
Don't worry about it, Lex
别担心 Lexi
That's good work for today. She's all yours
今天就到此为止 她就交给你了
Excuse me?
你说什么？
We've got to create a buzz
我们得来点造势
I want the whole skating world to know
you're a force to be reckoned with
我要让整个滑冰届知道你是不可忽视的势力
Hey, you. 嗨
Hey. What time is it? 嗨 现在几点了?
I don't know
不知道
I'm having a serious affair with your voicemail these days
最近只能频繁和你的来电语音对话
I know. I'm sorry. I had a lot of practice and then Coach sent me shopping
我知道 真是对不起 我一直在训练 教练又要我去购物
Shopping? I guess I could see how you
can't find time to answer my messages, huh?
购物？我还以为你忙的没时间回复我的留言
Well, I'm sorry. I just haven't had time
对不起 我真的没时间
What the heck's that noise?
那是什么声音？
I'm getting my hair done
我在做头发
I thought you're there to skate, Lex
我还以为去那是为了滑冰 Lex
But, Nick...
但是 Nick..
You know, this sounds like bull to me
你知道..这听起来很扯
I gotta practice in a couple of hours, Lex.I can barely hear you
我再过一两个小时就要去训练了  我几乎听不到你说话
What?
什么?
Yeah, exactly. I gotta run.
我得走了
Wonderful. I love you. You're beautiful. You're great. Oh, good. There you go.
Just one more smile for me. Thank you.
太美了 真是爱你 好极了 很好 就是这样 再笑一个 谢谢
Perfect. Good. Now, spin, turn. Pose, smile
完美 非常好 现在转圈 转身 摆姿势 笑一个
Oh, get that out of your face. Okay. Good.Teeth. Very nice.I think we have it
要笑开来 露出牙齿 很好 我想我们拍好了
Is it awful?
看起来很糟吗?
Awful? No. It's not awful
很糟？ 不 才不会
Believe me, it is a far cry from anything but beautiful
相信我 除了美丽再也没有别的评语了
This is Lexi Winston, my newest skater
这是Lexi Winston 我的最新弟子
Do you think she'll make it to sectionals?
你觉得她可以进入分区赛吗？
Isn't Carrie Turner favoured?
Carrie Turner是否更有竞争力？
I wish her only the best,but I'm very excited about Miss Winston's regional debut
我祝福Carrie   但我兴奋于Winston小姐的首次地区赛亮相
Dad. Aunt Jane.
爸爸 Jane阿姨
You guys made it
你们真的来了
You couldn't have kept us away
我们怎么能缺席
Hi, Mr Winston. How are you doing?
Winston先生 你好吗？
Good. Thank you
很好 谢谢
Jane
Bad or good?
好看吗？
Who is this incredibly beautiful young woman here?
这位美的惊人的小姐是谁？
Really? 真的吗？
Yeah, really 真的
Lexi, hurry. We're up next.Lexi, let's go.
Lexi 快点 下个轮到你 Lexi 我们走
Good luck 祝你好运
Thank you 谢谢
She's all grown up
她长大了
Performance makeup
表演化妆需要
Scores for Ms Turner Technical, 63.8. Components, 64.6 For a combined first place total of 128.4
得分 技术分 63.8 节目内容分64.6 总分128.4 暂列第一
Be careful. It's slippery out there
小心哦 这里很滑
She's trying to rattle you
她是想吓你
Yeah, well, I'm rattled enough as it is
我知道 我已经够怕了
Well, shut it out. You can do this
别理她 你可以做到
Hey, Lexi, skate the program and you'll be fine
Lexi 好好滑这套节目 你会好的
You're better than she is. Okay?
你比她好 知道吗？
Our next skater this evening,representing the Boston Skating Club,Boston, Massachusetts— Lexi Winston
今晚的下一位选手代表波士顿俱乐部，波士顿市麻省州—Lexi Winston
Wow! Sweetie, you were fantastic
哇！亲爱的 你真是太棒了！
The scores for Ms Winston.Technical, 49. 15. Components, 71. 18. For a combined total of 120.33
得分：技术分49.15 节目内容分71.18 总分120.33
putting her solidly in second place
and on her way to sectionals
稳坐第二位 确定晋级分区赛
You did it. You did it
你做到了 你做到了
Is this really your first competition?Are you guys together?
这真是你第一次比赛吗？你们两个在一起吗？
How long have you been training with Aiden Reynolds?
你和Reynolds在一起训练多久了？
Where'd you find this gem, Aiden?
Aiden,你在哪里发现这块璞玉？
On a pond in Lowa
在爱荷华的池塘
Is she your new Carrie Turner? Do you think she has what it takes?
她是你的新Carrie Turner吗？你觉得她有潜力吗？
What do you think?
你觉得呢？
I think I'd like to do a story on her in Skating magazine
我觉得我想让她上滑冰杂志
All right. Absolutely
绝对没问题
That was a great run, Lexi
Lexi 你滑的很棒
You ever pull a stunt like that again and you're out
再像那样玩花样你就别练了
What?
什么
You don't add,change or place a jump unless I tell you to
不要增加、更改或加入跳跃动作除非我告诉你这么做
I tell you to do a triple, you do a triple.I don't, you don't
我叫你做三周 你就做三周 我没叫 你就别跳
I knew I could do it and I did it
我知道我有能力做 我就做了
It was sloppy
太草率了
I placed second
但我是第二名
Well, you think you know something because you've been doing this a little while?
只是经过短短的练习你就以为自己掌握了？
You don't.You need to always skate the program
你还没有 你需要不断滑这套节目
I have calculated every point, and competition is not the time to throw in something untrained
我已经计算好了每一分 比赛不是贸然丢出未经训练动作的时候
I'm sorry
对不起
This is your job and mine,and if you don't want to do it,go home with your dad right now.
这是你和我的责任 如果你不想这么做 现在就和你爸回家去
Please.... just let me stay
请..让我留下来
Go. Go say goodbye to your family
去 去和你的家人告别
Hey, Nick. It's me
嘿 Nick 是我
We seem to keep missing each other
看来我们一直错过对方
Busy schedules.But we knew that would happen
忙碌的日程 不过我们都知道会这样
I miss you
我想你
After regionals, it seems more than usual
地区赛过后 好像更常这样了
I can't wait to come to your game
我等不及要去看你比赛
I miss you. I already said that
我想你   我已经说过了
Call me back. Bye
给我回电话 再见
Lover boy?
男朋友？
He scored a goal at practice
他在训练打进一球
You better not let coach catch you talking on the phone
最好别让教练抓到你在打电话
He wants you here 150%
他要你150%投入训练
I barely talk to him
我几乎没和他通过话
Yeah, well, barely is better than never
which is how it usually ends up
是啊 几乎没有比从来没有好 通常感情就是这么结束的
We haven't seen each other in so long
我们好久没见面了
With all that's happened,do you really miss him that much?
经历了这一切 你真的这么想他吗？
What are you talking about?
I never thought I'd make it to sectionals
你在说什么？ 我从没想过我会晋级分区赛
Maybe I could change my flight,then I'd only miss a few practices
也许我可以改改航班 这样只会少训练几次
Hahaha Good luck
哈哈哈 祝你好运
Hey, it's Lexi. I'm probably skating, but if you leave me a message, I'll call you back
这是Lexi 我可能在滑冰 如果你留言 我会回电话
Hey, I got you a really good seat right by the tunnel
嘿   我帮你在通道旁留了一个很好的位置
so I'll give you a wave when I come out
我出场时会和你挥手
And I look forward to seeing you tomorrow night
期待明天能看到你
What's the matter? 怎么了？
Nothing 没事
What?
什么？
How do you know? 你怎么知道？
Please 拜托
I'm supposed to go to Michigan for Nick's first game
我应该去密歇根看Nick的第一场比赛
You've got sectionals coming up
你快要参加分区赛了
I'd only miss two days of practice
我只会错过两天的练习
I thought we had this conversation
我想我们已经讨论过这事了
Peterson, get in there
Peterson  到那去
Well, that's it, folks.A warm round of applause for another Michigan State victory
结果揭晓 请为密歇根州立又赢得一场胜利而鼓掌
It's me. I'm so sorry
是我 真的很抱歉
I really wanted to be there.I did everything I could I'm sure you did great. You always do.
我真的很想去 也尽了最大的努力 我确定你表现的很好 你一直都很棒
So, Ms Winston, do you have a boyfriend?
Winston小姐 你有男朋友吗？
I do. He's a hockey player at Michigan State
我有 他是密歇根州的一位冰球选手
Excuse me  打断一下
Sure you want that on record?
你确定要这样回答吗？
Why not?
为什么不？
I don't know.Something happens between you two...
要是你们两个之间有...
We're fine
我们很好
I'm sure you are,but a little mystery never hurt either
我知道 但不说出来也无妨
So have you got your story straight?
所以你们想好怎么说了吗？
I'm with Lexi Winston who can barely contain her excitement First major competition...
我正在访问Lexi Winston 她很兴奋 第一次重要比赛...
So doing this well, do you have goals now?
Have your goals changed?
你表现的很好，你现在有目标吗？你的目标变了吗？
No one even knew your story. You came in
之前你默默无闻 你突然出现
You had grown up in lowa,skating on ponds, as you say.Did you dream about a day like this?
成长于爱荷华，你说你在池塘上滑冰，会想到有今天吗？
It's fun to be recognized
能被人肯定很高兴
Media darling Lexi Winston is taking the ice skating world by storm
媒体宠儿Lexi Winston在滑冰届掀起旋风
You know, you always dream about it,but you never really think that it's gonna happen
你一直梦想着这一刻 却不曾真的认为会梦想成真
How do you handle that pressure?
你如何处理那种压力？
I don't think of it as pressure.I think of it as excitement
我不认为这是一种压力 我认为是值得高兴的事
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! This is so awesome
我的天！ 我的天！ 太棒了！
Turn to page 25
翻到第25页
I told you it's be worth it
我就说一切都值得
This is amazing.This is so cool! This is awesome!
太令人惊讶了 好酷 好棒！
Read the cover
看看封面
"Lexi Winston, from Lowa to l-oh-wow.""To l-oh-wow."
Lexi Winston 从爱荷华 到 我 喔 哇
Did you get the magazine?
你有那本杂志吗？
Yup.You're like a celebrity now.
恩 你现在像个名人了
I kind of am. It's crazy
可以这么说 太疯狂了
What happened to you?
你怎么了？
Nothing. I'm just sore
没事 我只是肩膀痛
I have sectionals next weekend
我下周末有分区赛
What about Thanksgiving?
感恩节怎么办？
Well, I was hoping maybe you could come here to Boston
我希望你能到波士顿
I thought you were coming here to Michigan
我还以为你会来我这边 到密歇根
I can't, I have practice
我不能 我要训练
Yes. So do I
是的 我也有
Well, I want to see you
我想见你
Why does it say you're single?
为什么报道说你单身？
What?
什么？
The magazine says you're single
这个杂志说你单身
That wasn't me. That was Aiden He said that I should probably just try to keep us quiet
那不是我说的 是Aiden的意思 他说也许不公开比较好
You kidding me, Lex?
你在开玩笑吗？Lex？
Nick, you know what? We knew this was gonna be hard and it is.
Nick 听我说好吗 我们都知道这很难处理 事实也是如此
It stinks, but we said we would make it work.
We said we would make it happen
这很糟 但我们要克服 我们要成功
Yeah, well, look, it's not working.You know we haven't seen each other in a really long time
可是却无法克服 你知道我们很久没见面了
and we haven't talked at all,and every time I do talk to you,
you're not even there.
我们很久没通过话了 每次我想找你讲话 你都不在
I can't help it. I'm doing the best I can.
这是迫不得已的 我已经在尽力了
You can't help being a different person?
你变了个人是迫不得已的吗？
I'm trying
我在努力不要
Maybe we should just take a break
也许现在我们该休息一下了
This isn't working
这行不通了
Are you all right? 你还好吗？
I'm fine 我很好
Are you sure? 你确定？
Yeah. I said I'm fine, okay? 是的 我说了我很好
So that's it?
就这样？
I didn't get recruited to get my butt kicked for nothing.
I'm good enough to play
我进球队不是为了做板凳  我够资格上场
Sorry you see it that way
很抱歉你会这么想
Don't think I'm gonna beg you to stick around
别以为我会求你留下
I've got a winning team here
我的球队很优秀
So as far as I can see,you're doing me a favor
所以你的离开也算是帮了我一个忙
Sit 上车
Are you kidding me? 你在开玩笑吗？
The only way I'm getting on this is if I'm driving
我唯一会坐这东西的时候就是我开车的时候
You know how?
你会开？
I'm from Lowa
我来自爱荷华
Hold on
坐好了
Boy, you're full of surprises
噢！你真令人意想不到
You don't know the half of it.
还不止这些呢
Are you concerned about her, though
as you get ready for sectionals?
你在准备分区赛时会担心她的威胁吗？
I don't think so. I'm just... I can take it in stride
我不觉得 我觉得我可以冷静面对
and I'm working really hard
and I have full confidence going into sectionals. So...
而且我很努力 我对分区赛很有信心 所以...
So you don't feel like you have to look over your shoulder at her?
所以你不担心她会赢过你？
No, definitely not. 不 完全不担心
Okay, good luck. 好的 祝你好运
Thank you very much 非常感谢
底特律 中西部
全美锦标赛分区女单决赛
附：全美锦标赛 Regional(地区)→Sectional(分区)→National（全国）
Aiden, do you think Ms Winston has a shot at nationals?
你认为Winston小姐有机会进入全国赛吗？
We wouldn't be here if I didn't
要是没把握我们就不会在这里了
But do you think she's skating well enough to beat Carrie Turner?
但你认为她有能力打败Carrie Turner吗？
I think Ms Winston can beat anyone competing today
我认为Winston小姐可以打败今晚的任何人
What about regionals,a little bit of beginner's luck there maybe?
地区赛呢 是否有新人的运气成分？
No. Pure talent and hard work
没有 纯粹靠天赋与付出
Hey, Lexi, are the rumours true?Is there a romance brewing?
Lexi 传言是真的吗？是否有恋爱在发酵？
I don't comment on my personal life,but thank you
我对私人生活不发表评价 谢谢关心
Facing one of the more interesting challenges in her career,
Carrie Turner is delivering the best performance we've seen.
面对职业生涯最有趣的挑战  Carrie Turner带来了她有史以来最好的表演
I have to agree.Now, the unknown element this evening is Lexi Winston
我同意 现在今晚的唯一悬念就是Lexi Winston
who came in a close second in the regionals
who can possibly top her second place finish here
她在地区赛中以接近冠军的分数取得了第二名,很有可能在今晚赢得冠军
Let me tell you something,
she is skating absolutely flawlessly this evening
让我告诉你们 Carrie Turner今晚的表演行云流水
Our next competitor,representing the Boston Skating Club in Boston, Massachusetts is Lexi Winston
下一位选手代表波士顿俱乐部，波士顿市麻省州—Lexi Winston
Amazing
太令人赞叹了
[The scores for Miss Winston. Technical, 70.1 Components, 81.3. For a combined total of 151.4
得分 技术分70.1 节目内容分81.3 总分151.4]
Nick? Nick,等等
[Ladies and gentlemen, we have a new sectionals champion, Lexi Winston
女士们先生们，新的分区冠军—Lexi Winston]
Lexi! Lexi, right here, please.Aiden! Aiden! Turn around, just...
Lexi 看这里 看这里 Aiden! Aiden!  转过来
Lexi, you look amazing
Lexi 你看起来美极了
You okay?
你还好吗？
Aiden, I'm nervous
Aiden 我很紧张
But that's just so great. It's all new, exciting Let's get to work
不过真的太棒了 全新的体验 令人兴奋 我们过去吧
Aiden how are you? Please, introduce us.
Aiden 你好吗 快来帮我们介绍
How are you? Of course, Diane, this is Lexi Winston.
你好吗？当然 Diane 这是Lexi Winston
You are just fantastic.Aiden's lucky to have found you
你表现的太棒了 Adien真幸运能找到你
Lexi, you are adorable...Your future is limitless, my dear
Lexi你真是令人喜爱  你真是前途无量 亲爱的
Monday morning, your office, 8:00 a. m? Absolutely
明早8点早你的办公室？ 没问题
The sky's the limit for you, dear
亲爱的 你的未来一片光明
Aiden, I want first dibs for our New Year's show for next year.You promised me
Adien 我要你将我明年的新年表演排在第一位 你答应过的
You know how we feel about your show,Eddie, but Ice Capades is very interesting
你知道我们对于你表演秀的看法 Eddie
但是《冰上历险》很有趣
You are just darling
你简直太美妙了
Excuse me for a second
抱歉失陪一下
What was that?
怎么了？
Can we just go?
我们可以离开吗？
Honey, do you have any idea who these people are?
What they could do for you?
甜心 你知道这些人都是谁吗？他们能给你带来什么？
I know, but..
我知道 但是
He is a big time ice show producer.If he likes you, you'll work year-round as long as you can skate. Trust me.
他是大牌商演的主办方
如果他喜欢你 只要你一直滑冰他都会重用你 相信我
Show that smile of yours,he's gonna love you.
来点笑容 他会喜欢的你
Look, you've got maybe a couple good years in this business
听好 你在这一行可能只有几年的好光景
Right now, you're an entertainer. We all are.Think I like this?
现在 你是艺人 我们都是 你以为我喜欢这样吗？
Can we just go somewhere? Just us.
可以到别的地方去吗？只有我们就好
Yeah, okay, we will. We will.Just give me one minute, okay
好 我们去 再等一分钟好吗
just talk to this producer, then we'll go ,okay? Be right back.
和这个制作人谈完就走好吗？ 马上回来
Hello. 你好
Hey, Daddy. 嘿 爸爸
Well, hello, sweetheart. How are you doing?
嗨 宝贝 你过得还好吗？
Good. No, everything's fine
好  一切都很好
Well, sounds like that means we won't be seeing you
听起来意味着我们短期内见不到你
Well, we still have a lot to do
and Aiden says we have to get ready for nationals
我们还有很多事要做   Aiden说我们还要准备全国赛
Daddy  爸爸
What is it, sweetheart? 怎么了 宝贝？
This might be a funny question,but do you think I'm all right?
这个问题可能很好笑 但你觉得我现在没问题吗？
Well, no, I think you're the most wonderful person in the world
but I'm not sure that I follow you
不 我觉得你是全世界最棒的 不过我不确定是否懂你
Me, neither
我自己也不懂
Say, maybe what you need to do is come home, you know, for a little bit and just..
也许你需要回家待一下..
If only. I'm sorry I'm not there, Daddy
如果能就好了 但是我不能在家真令人难过 爸爸
Yeah, me, too. Me, too.
我也很难过
Hey, listen, whatever you, you know, need to do
or want to do, I'm there for you, okay?
不管你需要什么还是想做什么 我永远支持你
Thanks
谢谢
I'm your dad
我是你爸爸
I love you, Daddy 我爱你 爸爸
I love you too, honey 我也爱你宝贝
I'll talk to you soon
下次再聊
Who is that?
那是谁？
Aiden
Can you say "desperate for attention?"
你想这是不是"拼命想引人注意"？
Lexi! Baby, don't move.
Lexi 孩子 别动
Call an ambulance! Somebody call an ambulance!
叫救护车！快叫救护车！
Why can't I see?
为什么我看不见？
No, I don't... I don't remember
我不 我什么都不记得了
Lexi, you bumped your head,
and they think you've got a concussion
Lexi 你撞到头了 医生认为你有脑震荡
You had an accident.You took a fall at the lake
你发生了意外 你在湖上跌掉
Everything's gonna be all right
一切都会没事的
Go back three slices.
回到这三张图
Well, her tests are consistent
她的测试结果很稳定
And that's a good thing?
这是好现象吗？
Once these things plateau,it's rare to see improvement but this light perception she has will remain
一旦状况稳定下来 就很难有进展 但是她对光线还是有知觉
So you're saying this is it?
所以现在的状况就是这样？
There are always miracles, new discoveries.
The brain is complex and unpredictable
医学界不乏有奇迹、新发现   脑部很复杂也很难预测
The fact that she can see some light will certainly help her
她还能看到一些光线 一定对她有帮助
What next?
接下来怎么做？
Go home
回家
Help her adjust to being blind,get back to some sense of normalcy
帮助她适应失明的状况 恢复平常作息
This is gonna be a big adjustment for her
这对她是很大的调整适应
And for you
对你来说也是
I spoke to the press
我对媒体说了
I still don't understand why it's any of their business
我还是不明白 这关他们什么事
I told them she broke her arm
我告诉他们她摔断了手臂
The doctors are keeping quiet.That should buy us some time
医生都保密   所以我们能隐瞒一阵子
at least until nationals, and by then they'll be on to other stories, so...
至少在全国赛之前不会报道这事真相 所以...
In the meantime, you can relax and lay low back in Lowa
and we'll see what happens
这段时间你可以放松在爱荷华静养 我们再看看情况如何
I can't see
我看不见
It's over
一切都完了
No, no The doctor said there's a chance
不 不 医生说还有希望
A chance?Are you saying that for me or for you?
希望？你这么说是为我还是为你自己？
I don't even know why you're here any more
我都不知道你为什么在这里
Just leave me alone. It's over
别管我 一切都结束了
No. No. No, Lexi. It's not over.
不 不 不 不 Lexi 还没有结束
You love skating and winning
你喜欢花滑也喜欢胜利
Nationals are coming, and then the season is gonna be over and it'll start up again
全国赛即将开始 这个赛季结束又是一个新赛季
You'll find yourself a new skater and she'll win gold for you
你会找到新选手 她会为你赢得金牌
That's all you ever wanted
这就是你想要的
Please just go
请离开
Aiden, just go
Aiden 走吧
Well, the big question in the figure skating world right now
花样滑冰届当前最关注的问题：
what happened to Lexi Winston?
Lexi Winston到底怎么了？
What we hear is that Lexi broke her arm at a non-competition event
现在得到的说法是她在非比赛场合摔断了手臂
but there seems to be more to it since it can't be confirmed
不过情况似乎更加严重 因为无法证实
There has been no press conference ,no calls answered
没有新闻发布会 电话也没有得到回应
In fact, Lexi has virtually disappeared from the scene
事实上 Lexi消失的无影无踪
Mysterious, to say the least
只能说 这是一个谜
They said it wasn't gonna snow,
but it sure doesn't feel that way
他们说不会下雪 但还是下了
I wouldn't know
我不会知道的
What's that?
什么？
I said I wouldn't know
我说我不会知道的
Come on. You can smell it in the air.I know you can
你从空气中就可以感觉到 我知道你可以
I should have never gone to Boston
我根本不该去波士顿
Lexi. Stop listening to your mind telling you what you don't have
Lexi 别再想什么不该去做
and what you should have done
和什么本该做
Let's just focus on what's here and right now
我们好好专注当下
Just try and feel the ground
试着感受这片土地
I couldn't be more proud of you.
You know that, don't you?
我以你为傲 你知道的 不是吗？
All I know is that I'm stuck here in
the middle of nowhere, in the dark
我只知道 我困在这里 不知何处 处在黑暗之中
That's very helpful  说这无济于事
It's true 但这是真话
Probably be stuck here forever
可能永远都困在这里
Listen, before you left here a few months ago, this wasn't nowhere
在你几个月离开之前 这里并非“不知何处”的地方
In fact, it was a place that you had a hard time leaving. Remember that?
而是你难以离开的地方 记得吗？
Welcome home, cutie
欢迎回家 可人儿
←金妍儿→
Hey. How was your sleep?
嘿 睡的好吗？
Okay
还好
Good. So I'm going out in a bit,and I could use the company
好  我要出去一下 想找你陪我去
No, thanks
不要 谢了
Come on, Lex.Why don't you come out for a bit?
别这样 Lex 你为什么不出去一下呢？
Ask Aunt Jane to go
找珍阿姨陪你去
Okay
好吧
Hot chocolate? With whipped cream
要喝热牛奶吗？加了奶泡的
I'm fine
不用了
It's beautiful out there today
今天天气很不错
Colder than cold, but at least it's not windy
冷的不得了 但至少风不大
We could go for a walk later.You could use the exercise
我们等下出去走走 你可以活动一下
No, thanks
不 谢了
It's been weeks, honey.The girls have been asking about you
都几个星期了宝贝 女孩们都在问你
What did you tell them?
你怎么跟她们说的？
Nothing. But everyone's gonna find out sooner or later
什么都没说 不过大家迟早会发现
So where is she?
她在哪里？
In her room
她房间
You're down here watching television
she's upstairs in her room doing what?
你在下面看电视 她在楼上房间做什么？
I don't know.I've read to her, I've talked to her
我不知道 我念过书给她听 也和她谈过了
You know, what is the point of you coming over here
if she's gonna be sitting upstairs by herself?
如果她要一个人待在楼上 你来这里是为了什么？
I can't make her do anything
我没办法叫她做别的事
She's dying up there
她会死在那里
Then you do something!
那你就做点什么！
I thought I was
我以为我做了
You know, why don't you come over? Okay
你何不过来一趟？ 好
All right. I've had enough of this.Come on, let's go
好 我受够了 起来 我们走
Dad
爸爸
Come on, let's go
起来 我们走
Dad
爸爸
Your mother would be ashamed of us
你妈妈会因为我们感到羞愧
You sitting around here feeling sorry for yourself for so long
and the fact that I actually helped you
你一直坐在这里自怨自艾   实际上我这是在帮你
Come on, let's go
起来 我们走
Leave me alone
别管我
It's lonelier in this house now than when you were in Boston
这房子比你去波士顿时还要冷清
Dad
爸爸
Come on, let's go
起来 我们走
Where? Where are we going?
哪里？我们去哪里？
Anywhere but here!
We are not gonna sit and rot in this house!
除了这里哪里都好 我们不能坐在这屋子里等着发霉！
Dad, I'm not ready for this
爸爸 我还没准备好
It's slippery
这很滑
That's why you're wearing skates
所以你穿着冰鞋
Is the ice thick enough?
冰结的够厚吗？
We're gonna find out soon enough, I think
我觉得我们等会就会知道了
Dad
爸爸
I just remember when your mum and I used to bring you out here
我记得以前你妈和我经常带你来这里
Yeah, you weren't too interested in walking
but you loved the feel of the ice.You loved it
那时你不喜欢走路 却喜欢滑冰的感觉
My legs are tired
我的双腿很疲惫
Yeah. Well, come on.It's just another minute. That's it
加油 撑一下就好
One foot in front of the other.You can remember
一只脚滑到另一只前面 你能记起来
Dad. Dad, I'm just not ready
爸爸  爸爸我还没准备好
When did you become such a wuss?
你什么时候变成胆小鬼了？
Nick? What are you doing here?
Nick? 你在这做什么？
You know, I'm getting kind of tired,
and my legs are kind of beaten. It's cold.
我累了 腿也很酸 天气很冷
Why don't you... Can you help me out here?
你何不....你能帮我吗？
No, Dad. Dad, I'll come with you
不要 爸 我和你一起走
What? You're gonna leave me out here by myself, huh?
什么？你要把我一个人丢在这里？
I said... Dad, just let me...
我说...爸爸...让我....
Hey, I got you
我抓住你了
I'm fine
我没事
I said I'm fine
我说我没事
It's my skates. It's my skates. I just...
是冰鞋的关系 冰鞋的关系
Yeah, it's gotta be your skates
是的 一定是冰鞋的关系
Can you help me get them off?
可以帮我脱下吗？
No, get up. Get up. Get up
不 起来 站起来 起来
Stop it
住手
All this time, Lex,I kept thinking to myself, "She's home.
Lex 我一直都在想着“她回家了"
"And she gets cabin fever"
"她得了幽居病"
"I guess she really doesn't want to see me."
“我想她不愿意见我”
Maybe she figured you wouldn't want to see her after what happened
也许她知道在发生这些事之后你不会想见她
Maybe he thought that he caused it
and he couldn't admit it to himself
也许他认为这些事是因他而起 而他却无法承认
Nick
I'm right here
我在这
Help me
帮我
I'm right here
我在这
Don't let me go
别放手
I'm right here
我在这
See? Look, look!
You can stand on your own...
看 看 你可以自己站着了
You okay? You used to fall all the time
你还好吗？ 你以前也经常跌倒
Nick, I can't see anything
Nick 我什么都看不到
Come on
起来
Just follow my voice, okay?
跟着我的声音好吗？
Do you think that maybe we could try this again?
你觉得也许我们可以重新开始吗？
Skating. Skating, I mean
滑冰 我是说滑冰
Are you sure that no one's gonna be here?
你确定没人在这里？
Jane said the girls will be coming in at 10:00
and we'll be out before then
Jane说女孩们10点开始练习 那时候我们已经离开了
You can still tie up your skates
你有的是时间绑紧鞋带
Now all I have to do is skate
我现在要做的事 只是滑冰
You feel good?
还好吗？
If you're gonna skate
we gotta figure out a way for you to see the walls
如果你要滑冰 我们得想个办法让你看到冰场围墙
That's a good idea, except I'm blind
好主意 只是我看不到
I know. What I mean is,is you're able to see light and shadow
我知道 我是说  如果你看得见光和影子
so maybe you can use that to get a feel for the rink
所以你也许可以用此来感觉冰场
See, there you go. That's good
看 你开始滑了 这很好
You're starting to get a sense of where the wall is now?
现在开始感觉到冰场围墙了吗？
Sort of
大概可以
All right, good
好的 很好
Nick？
You're fine 你没事
Lex, turn, turn...
Lex 转弯 转弯...
You okay? 你还好吗？
Yeah  恩
Now I know why you guys wear so much padding
我现在才知道你们为什么带这么多护具
Skate toward me and count out loud
往我这边滑 大声数出来
One one thousand, two one thousand,
three one thousand, four one thousand
一个一千   两个一千 三个一千 四个一千
You're halfway
你滑到冰场的一半了
Twenty feet, ten, five, stop. Good
20尺 10尺 5尺 好 停
No, this is too fast
不行 这样太快了
You get 10 feet, there you go, yeah
会有10尺缓冲 就这样 来
You just turned on your own! Good!
Come here. Come toward centre ice
你刚刚自己转弯了！太棒了！过来！到冰场中心来！
Hey, if you can balance in spread eagle,
you should be able to try a sit spin.
如果你能做出大一字 你应该可以试试蹲转
You're crossing the blue line now
你现在穿过蓝线
Don't tell me
别告诉我
Look at that. Here, skate toward me
滑得好 现在朝我这边滑过来
What was that, another blind joke?
这是什么 另一个不好笑的笑话？
Hey, try a jump!
嘿 试着做个跳跃！
No
不要
Just get some air.
What's the worst that could happen?
跳一下就好 最糟的情况会是怎样？
Well, I could fall on my butt,hit my head and go deaf
我可能摔个四脚朝天  撞到头 然后就聋了
How's that?
怎么样？
Well, hand me a stick and a puck, too
If you can hand them over here
给我球棍和球 如果你能拿到这里
Here you go 拿去
Okay 好
And let me know when I'm at the centre of this blue line, okay?
我到蓝线中央的时候让我知道好吗？
Blue line!
蓝线!
I knew it
我就知道
I knew where it was
我就知道这行得通
Come with me. I want to try something
跟我来 我要试点别的
What are we doing?
我们要做什么？
You will see. Follow me
跟我来就知道了
I'm better off in the rink
我最好去冰场
No, no, give it a shot
不要 试试看嘛
I don't even know where the edges are
我连边界在哪里都不知道
Sure you do
你知道的
Come on. I'll start you
来吧  我带你开始
Keep talking
继续说话
Hey, don't try to see
嘿 不要企图去看
I mean, if you can't see,maybe making the effort to do that
is just getting in the way of using something else
我是说 如果你看不见却努力想去看见  也许会妨碍使用另一种知觉
Like what?
例如什么？
The sound when I slam into the boards?
像我撞到挡板的声音吗？
No. Like your memory
不 例如你的记忆
Just close your eyes.Just picture it in your head
闭上眼睛 在你的脑海中描绘景象
Lex, we've been skating on this pond our whole lives.Nothing's changed
Lex 我们一直都在这池塘滑冰 这里没什么改变
It's the same shape, the same dimensions
形状没变  尺寸也没变
Come on. You've done this blindfolded before. What's the difference?
来吧 你以前蒙着眼睛都能做到  现在有什么区别？
I could cheat before
我以前可以作弊偷看
It's like lacing up your skates
You know, if you think about it too much
then you get all tangled up
就像绑冰鞋带一样 你一直想着绑鞋带 鞋带就会缠在一起
If you just do it, then it's second nature
如果不假思索的去做  就会变成自然动作
There you go
这就对了
You're approaching the middle.
You're about a third of the way to the end, Lex
你滑到中间了 你还有三分之一到达终点
Don't tell me 别告诉我
Okay 好
Okay. Where am I now?
我现在的位置在哪里？
You just told me not to tell you
你刚才说让我不要告诉你
I know where you are. Come on.
Where do you think you are?
我知道你的位置在哪 你觉得自己的位置在哪？
By the stream outlet.
在小溪的水口
Yes
是的
Look who's showing off, huh?
Watch the edge, 10 feet. Good
看看谁在炫耀 哈   小心边界 还有10尺 好的
Come on, come towards me
来吧 向我这边滑
Lex, you landed it! You okay?
Lex 你做到了 你还好吗？
That's incredible!
太惊人了！
I felt like that even when I could see
我觉得自己像是能看见的
You felt it?
你感觉到了？
Yeah
是的
It just kind of happened. How'd it look?
就这样发生了 你觉得如何？
Incredible
妙极了
It's good to see you smile, Lex
看到你的笑容真好
Is she ready yet?
她准备好了吗？
You should have some coffee
喝点咖啡吧
No, thanks. We gotta get going
不 谢了 我们要走了
Come on. It's not gonna kill you
拜托 又不会杀了你
Hey, I gotta tell you, she is, you know
我得告诉你 她准备好了 你知道的
I mean, I think you've pulled her out of her funk.
你把她低潮中解救出来
And that jump, you know, that she tried
还有....那个...她试着做出的跳跃
I mean, if you give her another couple of weeks and... That was a heck of a thing
如果再给她一两个星期 会很不得了
Well, if she could do it once,she could do it again
如果她能跳一次 就能跳第二次
Well, I guess that means
you're not planning on going any easier on her
我想这意味着你不打算让她放松脚步
Oh, she's tough. She can handle it
她很顽强 她可以胜任的
If you can just believe that you're on the pond, you can do it
你若当你在池塘上滑冰 你就可以做到
I'm not promising anything
我无法保证什么
Just pretend that the streamlet is to your left and go for it
假装小溪在你左边 然后滑过去
Yes! You did it!
太好了！你办到了！
Lex, you're skating beautifully
Lex 你滑的真美
I'm so proud of you
我为你感到自豪
Hey, Coach. Just hoping you might havea minute. Made a mistake
教练 占用你一点时间 我错了
I wish you could see the sunset, Lex
真希望你能看到日落 Lex
I'd rather see your face
我更希望看到你的脸
I miss you, Nick
我想你 Nick
I know you're right here, but I still miss you
我知道你就在这 但我仍想念你
I'm glad you got to see me skate at sectionals, I mean
很高兴你去看了我的分区赛比赛
It's too bad it's all over, though.
The skating part, I mean. Not the other stuff
真糟糕事情就这样结束了 我是说滑冰 不是说我们的关系
Maybe it doesn't have to be
也许事情不一定要这样
Yeah, right
是的 没错
Hey. You earned a spot at nationals
你晋级全国赛了
I checked. You're still registered
我查过了 你还在名单上
You checked?
你查过了？
Yeah,that guy called about your music
是的 有人打电话来问你要用的曲目
You can do it
你可以做到
Have you been thinking about this?
你一直有考虑这事吗？
It wouldn't work. I...
没用的...我...
Lex, I'm serious
Lex 我是说真的
So am I. It's ridiculous
我也是 这太荒谬了
Come on, it's not that crazy
拜托 这没那么疯狂
it's a little bit crazy,but why not?
好吧是有一点疯狂 但试一下又何妨？
Well, it's one thing for her to skate with you on the ice
有你陪在旁边滑冰是另一回事
She's skating great on her own
她自己也滑的很好
What difference does it make where she skates?
在不同场地有什么差别？
It's a big difference
有很大差别
Hey, she landed a triple
She's skating as well as ever
嘿 她成功了三周跳 她滑的和以前一样好
I don't have a program and I don't have a coach
我没有节目 也没有教练
But what about Jane?
Jane怎么样？
I could try, I suppose. I don't know
也许我能试试看 我不确定
Do you trust me?
你信任我吗？
Sure I do, but it's ridiculous
当然 但这太荒谬了
She can do it.She skated well enough at sectionals to win
她做得到 她是分区赛冠军
She beat out everyone in the middle of this country
她打败了国家中部所有高手
She qualified for nationals.
她赢得了全国赛入场券
But they'll pity me
但大家只会同情我
Yeah, they would if they knew
他们如果知道可能会
They will
他们会知道的
I don't know how they couldn't.
他们怎么可能不知道
The girls in the rink have seen you skate,they don't know
冰场上看过你练习的女孩 她们不知道
Give yourself a chance to prove...
给你自己一个机会去证明...
What?
证明什么？
...that it was all worth it
证明这一切都值得
Blind or not, if she could do this,she could do anything
无论是否失明 如果她能做到这个 任何事都难不倒她
This feels big
感觉好大
It's just like ours
就像是我们的专属冰场
Well, we've got as much time as we want
between 1:00 and 4:00 in the morning for the next few days
接下来的几天从凌晨1点到4点 我们有足够的使用时间
All right, just like home
好的 像在家一样
We'll count off the length and width dimensions
我们要计算出冰场长宽尺寸
and you enter from the centre end
你从中间的地方进去
So I just come straight out?
所以我就直接滑过去？
Yeah
对
If we start you off right, you'll be fine.
It'll be the same count
如果我们一开始做对就没问题 就用以前的计算方法
It's really just about balance and instinct
和平衡和直觉有关 开始吧 来这边
Here you go, just come here come towards the centre.
Ten feet, five, you're here, good
开始吧来这边 往中央去 10尺 5尺 很好
You'll start facing the entrance
你开始会面向入口
Here we go. And the judges will be right over here to your left
裁判会在你的左边
Twenty-five, ten, five
20 10 5
Hey. Attagirl
嘿 做得好
Today's national championship has attracted skating's royalty
今天的全美锦标赛吸引了花滑天后—
Michelle Kwan, five-time world championand nine-time US national champion
关颖珊, 5届世锦赛冠军，9届全美锦标赛冠军
←Sandra Bezic
关颖珊→
Carrie Turner is skating beautifully at this point in her career
在职业生涯的此刻 Carrie Turner滑的很美
She's in great position for the world championships and making the Olympic team next year
她会在世锦赛和明年奥运会国家队中脱颖而出
if she can avoid injury
如果她能避免伤病
Lexi?
You look...
你看起来...
How are you? I mean, does this mean you can...
你还好吗？这是不是意味着你能够...
No
看不见
Wow, you can't tell, it's amazing
看不出来 真是太惊人了
Aiden, this wasn't your fault
Aiden 这不是你的错
You were my responsibility
我对你有责任
I was my responsibility
我对自己负责
But I want you to know that I appreciate everything you did
但是我想要让你知道 我感激你所做的一切
It was all worth it
一切都是值得的
It was good seeing you, Lexi
看见你真好 Lexi
No one knows
没人知道
How would they?
他们怎么会知道？
She wants to keep it that way
她想要那样
Kick butt out there
好好表现
Hey, beautiful
嘿 美人儿
Just like practice, okay?
像训练一样 好吗？
In this season,she seems to have come from nowhere
这个赛季  她似乎从某个地方冒出来
and then she disappeared and now she's back
然后她消失 现在她又回来了
Well, since sectionals,everybody's been talking about Lexi
分区赛之后 每个人都在谈论Lexi
The crowd adores her and there's something real special about her skating
观众都很喜欢她 她的表演有种特别之处
There's a pureness, there's an honesty
纯净 坦诚
and she's able to emotionally connect with every single person in the audience
她可以和在场的每一位观众进行情感交流
Our next competitor, representing Ice Castle Skating Club in Windsor, Iowa is
下一位参赛者 代表冰上城堡俱乐部,温莎,爱荷华—
Lexi Winston
She certainly skates with joy and freedom and love
她的滑冰确实伴随着喜悦、自由和爱
and it seems to her it doesn't matter about winning or losing
but enjoying what she does
她似乎不在乎输赢与否 而只是享受其中
But the question is, is she capable of performing like that here now just coming fresh from an injury,having absolutely no experience
但是问题是 才从伤病中恢复 完全没有经验的她
Can she do it now when it counts?
还能那样表演吗？
Well, I guess we'll soon find out
我想我们很快就能看到答案
I thought you'd never come
我以为你不会过来
We forgot about the bears
我们忘记还会有玩偶了
I think they know now. Come on
我想他们现在知道了 来吧
金妍儿-花痴字幕组
听译/时间轴/压制：UZDA
协助: Joanna Sheep Tracy
www.weibo.com/yunakim